{
	"response_code": "0",
	"results": [
		{
			"category": "History",
			"type": "boolean",
			"difficulty": "medium",
			"question": "The two atomic bombs dropped on Japan by the United States in August 1945 were named &#039;Little Man&#039; and &#039;Fat Boy&#039;.",
			"correct_answer": "False",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"True"
				
			]
		},
		{
			"category": "History",
			"type": "boolean",
			"difficulty": "medium",
			"question": "The first televised presidential debate was between Jimmy Carter and Gerald Ford.",
			"correct_answer": "False",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"True"
				
			]
		},
		{
			"category": "History",
			"type": "boolean",
			"difficulty": "medium",
			"question": "In World War II, Hawker Typhoons served in the Pacific theater.",
			"correct_answer": "False",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"True"
				
			]
		},
		{
			"category": "History",
			"type": "boolean",
			"difficulty": "medium",
			"question": "Sargon II, a king of the Neo-Assyrian Empire, was a direct descendant of Sargon of Akkad.",
			"correct_answer": "False",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"True"
				
			]
		},
		{
			"category": "History",
			"type": "boolean",
			"difficulty": "medium",
			"question": "&quot;I disapprove of what you say, but I will defend to the death your right to say it&quot; is a quote from French philosopher Voltaire.",
			"correct_answer": "False",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"True"
				
			]
		},
		{
			"category": "History",
			"type": "boolean",
			"difficulty": "medium",
			"question": "Brezhnev was the 5th leader of the USSR.",
			"correct_answer": "True",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"False"
				
			]
		},
		{
			"category": "History",
			"type": "boolean",
			"difficulty": "medium",
			"question": "If you grab the bladed end of a longsword in a specific way, you will not cut yourself.",
			"correct_answer": "True",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"False"
				
			]
		},
		{
			"category": "History",
			"type": "boolean",
			"difficulty": "medium",
			"question": "Theodore Roosevelt Jr. was the only General involved in the initial assault on D-Day.",
			"correct_answer": "True",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"False"
				
			]
		},
		{
			"category": "History",
			"type": "boolean",
			"difficulty": "medium",
			"question": "In 1967, a magazine published a story about extracting hallucinogenic chemicals from bananas to raise moral questions about banning drugs.",
			"correct_answer": "True",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"False"
				
			]
		},
		{
			"category": "History",
			"type": "boolean",
			"difficulty": "medium",
			"question": "Abraham Lincoln was the first U.S. President to be born outside the borders of the thirteen original states. ",
			"correct_answer": "True",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"False"
				
			]
		}
	]
}